German Bulavkin

Contacts

Serbia, Novi Sad Location: +381621257346 Mobile: E-mail: thewhitehaven04@gmail.com Portfolio: https://gbulavk.in github.com/thewhitehaven04 GitHub:

Front-end engineer

Front-end engineer enthusiastic about web application performance, JavaScript language and library internals, and delivering quality software. Experienced in working in international teams. Fluent in English. My vast background in quality assurance will help you bridge the gap in understanding between development and testing.

Experience

March 2024 - December 2024

Junior Frontend Developer

Stenn International (Fintech)

Developmed back-office tooling for automation of compliance- and fraud reviews Migrated the product's team features to the internal design system UI kit

April 2020 - November 2022

QA Automation Engineer IBS Appline

Performed Ul and API testing of weband SAP-based applications

December 2022 - February 2024

QA Automation Engineer Stenn International (Fintech)

Conducted automated testing of user interfaces and APIs (pytest + Selenium) Optimised the product team's testing practices and coverage

July 2019 - Febrary 2020 **Junior QA Engineer Bytex LLC**

Education

September 2015 - June 2019 N.P. Ogarev Mordovia State University Bachelor's degree in Computer Science

Languages

- Russian (native)
- English (C1)

Soft skills

- Time managment
- Workload estimation
- Experience working in agile teams (SCRUM)
- Writing documentation
- Providing technical expertise during grooming sessions

References

Available upon request

Hard Skills

- HTML
- JavaScript/TypeScript
- CSS/CSS-in-JS
- React Router/Remix
- SSR
- Single-page applications

- Single-page applications
- Tailwind
- React Hook Form
- React Ouerv
- CI/CD (Azure CI, Jenkins) Jest/vitest/React Testing Library
 - Vite/Webpack
 - Node.js
 - Express